So today, a total solar eclipse will cross North America, a phenomena that has not occurred in the United States in seven years, and that astronomers say will not occur again in the U.S. for another 20 years.
But here's the other part of this.
Inmates in New York are suing the State Corrections Department over the decision to lock down prisons during the total solar eclipse.
The lawsuit argues that the lockdown violates inmates' constitutional rights to practice their faiths by preventing them from participating in a religiously significant event.
I think that's cap, but whatever it takes.
If y'all sat around and came up with that, it was brilliant, and I say run it.
But I am curious, like, when they all came up with this idea and said, like, let's put this together, like, let's put this on paper, like, what did that sound like?
So this is what we, this is our version of the letter to the warden, okay?
Dear Mr. Warden, why are you tripping?
These inmates is just asking to witness a celestial event, not have their side chick pay a conjugal visit under the cover of darkness.
Do you remember that scene in Shawshank Redemption where they tarred the roof under the scorching sun?
Hell, they played a movie on TNT 50-11 times a day.
Anyway, as Morgan Freeman put it, we sat and drank with the sun on our shoulders and felt like free men.
That's all these guys want, to feel like free men.
Well, not with the sun on their shoulders because the sun is going to be blocked, but you know what we mean.
Sincerely, us.